https://www.gelaw.com/privacy-policy/

Personally Identifiable Information Collection
Grant & Eisenhofer P.A. respects the privacy of its personnel, clients and alumni, as well as law students and other third parties. Users do not have to submit any personally identifiable information, or information that may identify, contact, or locate a person or to identify an individual in context, in order to use any Grant & Eisenhofer website. Personally identifiable information includes contact information necessary to support business relationships with Grant & Eisenhofer and the user. Personally identifiable information is not collected via the website unless it is specifically and voluntarily provided by a user.
Certain personal information for the firm’s educational, networking, marketing, social, recruiting and similar business purposes may be collected and processed on a Grant & Eisenhofer website. Such personally identifiable information that is voluntarily submitted to Grant & Eisenhofer is not shared with outside entities other than appropriate service providers who assist Grant & Eisenhofer in carrying out these business functions. Such personal information is not sold by Grant & Eisenhofer P.A.
Security
Grant & Eisenhofer provides appropriate and reasonable physical, procedural and electronic information security measures to protect such personal information. Personally identifiable information that is voluntarily submitted to Grant & Eisenhofer online, via electronic communication or otherwise, may be maintained or accessed in servers or files located in the United States.
Non-Personal Data Collection
To ensure that Grant & Eisenhofer’s websites are well managed and to facilitate improved navigation within it, various technologies, such as navigational data collection and web beacons (electronic images that allow web sites to count visitors who have accessed a particular page) may be used to track information and identify categories of visitors by items such as IP address, domain, browser type and pages visited. This information is used to analyze the number of visitors to different areas of Grant & Eisenhofer websites and to ensure that they are serving as useful, effective information sources. These technology tools are not used to collect any personally identifiable information such as name or email address.
Disclosure of Information to Third Parties
Notwithstanding the above referenced privacy policy, Grant & Eisenhofer may disclose personal information in special cases as noted:
When Grant & Eisenhofer has reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) the rights of Grant & Eisenhofer P.A. or property or anyone that could be harmed by such activities;
When Grant & Eisenhofer believes in good faith that the law requires it; and
In situations involving threats to the physical safety of any person.
User Consent
Use of this site constitutes the user’s consent to application of appropriate laws, rules and regulations. By using this site, the user agrees with the terms of this Privacy Policy.
Changes to the Privacy Policy
Grant & Eisenhofer P.A. reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Statement. All changes will be posted on this page.
485 Lexington Ave.
Copyright © 2020 Grant & Eisenhofer P.A. All Rights Reserved.
Settlement Information
